let quizQuestions = [
  { 
    question: "question-1 question-1 question-1",
    choice1: "question-1 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-1 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-1 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-1 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 2
  },
  { 
    question: "question-2 question-2 question-2",
    choice1: "question-2 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-2 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-2 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-2 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 1
  },
  { 
    question: "question-3 question-3 question-3",
    choice1: "question-3 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-3 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-3 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-3 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 3
  },
  { 
    question: "question-4 question-4 question-4",
    choice1: "question-4 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-4 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-4 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-4 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 4
  },
  { 
    question: "question-5 question-5 question-5",
    choice1: "question-5 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-5 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-5 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-5 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 2
  },
  { 
    question: "question-6 question-6 question-6",
    choice1: "question-6 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-6 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-6 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-6 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 1
  },
  { 
    question: "question-7 question-7 question-7",
    choice1: "question-7 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-7 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-7 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-7 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 3
  },
  { 
    question: "question-8 question-8 question-8",
    choice1: "question-8 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-8 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-8 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-8 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 2
  },
  { 
    question: "question-9 question-9 question-9",
    choice1: "question-9 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-9 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-9 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-9 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 4
  },
  { 
    question: "question-10 question-10 question-10",
    choice1: "question-10 choice-1",
    choice2: "question-10 choice-2",
    choice3: "question-10 choice-3",
    choice4: "question-10 choice-4",
    id: 'xxx',
    answer: 2
  }
]